go to the ruins of guy a crime flying the control room and within the master override.
This will give you the power to courage.
Haiti's so long as you find a way to wield Do not attempt repair of the system core until Haiti's is eradicated.
Haiti's must be destroyed.
That is home.
I only wish that I could hear your voice again.
Snow.
It's not getting any warmer out here.
I haven't been here in years.
I wonder what I could find.
Okay,
Yeah.
Your question.
Waiting for an answer.
Yeah,
you
area back there.
I wonder if I can find a way into it Now that I'm older.
Director Evans, Flash traffic from U.
S.
R.
C.
Black courts encryption averted the message to your hollow growth for viewing
another power self.
I only need one more to get to that ancient armour I found
from Director Evans to all subject all good things to all staff.
I regret to inform you that our worst fears have been realised.
Wichita salient has collapsed and our position will be overrun in less than 24 hours.
As I'm sure you understand, ex filtration transport is not available If you wish to abandon the facility and try your luck on foot, you may do so.
Locked too will unseal a 21 100 hours and remain unsealed for 15 minutes.
Godspeed.
For those who'd rather not die on our feet, there will be a gathering in the community room at 2200 hours.
And Nurse Hana will make other means available.
I want to underscore how proud I am of each and every person who served at this post.
It is important to bear in mind that our sacrifices were not in vain.
I hope that makes this a little easier.
For months now, I've been signing off messages as Director Evans.
But I suppose we can dispense with such formalities now.
Respectfully, Ellen.
No space.
I need them soon enough.
Okay.
Because machines are alert.
Got you
that.
Here I am.
Thank you.
I like it.
Girl.
What are you doing with that machine?
What?
The way to the mountain will be hard, ferocious machines, proud.
Every step of the climb more corrupted.
Not cool.
Really?
You?
Yeah.
Stalkers in the open watchers on the other side.
This will help.
Yeah,
you
do.
They think they're guarding guy.
I don't think it all
more like an instant.
Give them to grace.
You know what?
Their garden.
More than a quick to take you on.
No,
no,
down you go.
I guess I'm almost there.
Correct.
I can't get out of this.
They come
a week.
Fluids
burns at my fingers with corruption.
Does
don't talk that a way.
It's cold.